

Ananya

Kurukshetra, Haryana, India

E-mail: ananya1703@gmail.com

Website:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ananyanurekha/

Phone: 9996440802

SUMMARY

Experienced UI developer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in C+ +,Javascript,HTML5,CSS, and jQuery. Currently enrolled in executive post graduation programme in Software Development from IIIT Bangalore, specializing in full stack development

WORK EXPERIENCE

Amtex Systems Pvt Ltd

Jan 2017 — June 2018

Associate Consultant Junior UI Developer

Created physical and prototype designs and functions for websites. Basically responsible for working on the look and feel of the products.

Insight Centre for Data Analytics,Ireland Jul 2015 — Sep 2015

International Student Intern

Worked on constraint Programming using Java to develop an application for car pooling and traffic management.

EDUCATION

Executive PG Programme in, Software development

2021 - 2022

International Institute of Information Technology Bangalore

Specializing in Full Stack development.

B Tech. Computer Science

2012 - 2016

Kurukshetra University

SKILLS

HTML • Java Script • CSS • Jquery • C++ • Bootstrap • Spring boot

AWARDS & HONOURS

Digital India Hackathon 2016 - ACM India

In September 2016 ACM India organised a hackathon as the one-day digital India event in conjunction with VLDB 2016 and Persistent Systems Ltd. The Digital India Hackathon consisted of online and offline participation revolving around 5 themes. Among 9061 participants the short listed teams were called for offline round for final presentation and demonstration. Was among top 13 teams selected for the offline round.

Ananya